Clovis Kyndt

Software Engineer

About

I'm Clovis, a senior software engineer who craft products and make nice things to automate process. I'm curious of all technologies related to web, mobile and data, user interaction and experience.

Apart from hi-tech field, I like running, swimming, hiking, and traveling. During my master study, I have had one year exchange experience in China, which finally interests me to explore more in the culture and learn Chinese.

Stack

Langages	Data	Interests
Python	PostgreSQL	Product development
Golang	MongoDB	Code quality
Typescript	Kafka	Architecture
Rust	MS SQL	Data visualization
Framework	Operations	Extra
Vue	Kubernetes	Team management
FastAPI	AWS & Azure	Collaboration
Flutter	Terraform	Communication

Work Experience

Numberly Software Engineer March 2016 - Present | Paris, France Built a suite of apps to drive operational excellence and performance in omnichannel campaigns.

- Worked on solutions using Python, Golang, Vue, SQL, Kafka
- Defined and developed quality processes according to the growth of the team's organization
- Manage authentication domain accountability, collabor with clients to integrate their system
- Collaborate, deliver and communicate architecture solutions

Altran Software Engineer Intern

October 2015 - March 2016 | Lille, France

Built a web application with AngularJS and ASP.NET to visualize crop plots, forecasting and suggesting countermeasures against fungicide risks according to various parameters and provide automated reporting to each user.

Libertrip Backend Developer Intern

April 2014 - August 2014 | Lille, France

Support dev team on the main application written in Ruby on Rail. Gather a large inventory of hotels through multiple providers and provide an interface in AngularJS to interact with the inventory.

Education

MSc Computer Science Epitech

September 2011 - September 2016 | Paris, France

MSc Computer Science (Exchange) Beijing JiaoTong University

September 2014 - July 2015 | Beijing, China

Languages

French

Native speaker

English

Fluent, lived six months in UK

Chinese

intermediate, lived a year in Beijing

